National Organization for Women, New York State Chapter; Records apap029
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Lobbyist Files, 1972-1988; 4; 2.7 cubic ft.
  - 43-Equitable distribution, A8497, 03/15/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 88)
  - 44-Sexual harassment, A617, 03/18/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 89)
  - 45-Equitable distribution, A8497, 03/18/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 90)
  - 48-A3081, 03/22/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 91)
  - 49-Adultery, A1637, 03/22/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 92)
  - 50-Unemployment Insurance Law, A4800, 03/22/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 93)
  - 51-A7986, 03/29/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 94)
  - 52-Maternity care coverage, A5678B, 03/29/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 95)
  - 53-Medicaid funding for abortions, 03/26/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 96)
  - 54-Child support, S8485, A10813, 03/29/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 97)
  - 55-S8485, A10813, 04/01/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 98)
  - 56-Infant formula, A7986, 04/01/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 99)
  - 57-Maternity care coverage, A5678B, 04/01/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 100)
  - 58-Feiger, Sheila-mailings, 04/05/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 101)
  - 59-Joint custody, A10721, 04/19/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 102)
  - 60-Rape bills (3), 04/22/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 103)
  - 61-Sex discrimination, S221, A352, 04/22/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 104)
  - 62-Sex discrimination, A6022, 04/22/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 105)
  - 63-Abortion, S6561A, 04/24/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 106)
  - 64-Equitable distribution, A11516, A11562, S8735, 04/24/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 107)
  - 65-Equitable distribution, A11562, 04/30/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 108)
  - 66-Infant formula, A7986A, 04/30/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 109)
  - 67-Sex discrimination, S2827A, A3726A, 04/30/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 110)
  - 68-Abortion, A2340, 04/30/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 111)
  - 69-Sojouner Truth, 05/03/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 112)
  - 70-Alimony, A11363, S8967, 05/03/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 113)
  - 71-Age of support, S716, A1045, 05/03/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 114)
  - 72-Health, A2394, 05/03/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 115)
  - 73-Joint custody, S8464, A10721, 05/07/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 116)
  - 74-Divorce legal fees, A3105A, 05/10/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 117)
  - 75-Child support, A9760, 05/10/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 118)
  - 76-Life insurance, A7163, 05/10/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 119)
  - 77-Personal Property Law, A6292B, 05/28/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 120)
  - 78-Alimony, A2223A, 05/10/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 121)
  - 79-Maternity care, A5678B, 05/10/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 122)
  - 80-Beatrice Kachuck's letters to Freebone & Genrich, 05/07/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 123)
  - 81-Alimony and child support, A11363, S89967, 05/11/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 124)
  - 82-Joint custody, Hatfield/Hyde, 05/07/1982; 05/11/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 125)
  - 83-Abortion, S5410, S5204B, A6285, 05/17/1982; 05/24/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 126)
  - 84-Child support, A10813, 05/14/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 127)
  - 85-Child support, A10745A, 05/17/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 128)
  - 86-Divorce, A11, 101, 05/28/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 129)
  - 87-Parental leave, A4198, 05/17/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 130)
  - 88-Pension rights, S9401, A12385, 05/21/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 131)
  - 89-Workers Compensation survivors, A10081, 05/21/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 132)
  - 90-Equitable distribution, A11562, 05/24/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 133)
  - 91-Discrimination in employment, A6022, 05/21/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 134)
  - 92-Sex offenses, A5718, 05/21/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 135)
  - 93-Rape, S6355, A5538, 05/24/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 136)
  - 94-Sexual abuse, A5717A, 05/24/1982; 1982 June 7; 1982 June 10 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 137)
  - 95-legal services, S9443, A12403, 05/24/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 138)
  - 96-Strip searches, A7903, 06/09/1982; 1982 June 25 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 139)
  - 97-Exclusion of women from long shore jobs, A11892, 06/07/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 140)
  - 98-Education programs at Seneca Falls, A12821, 06/15/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 141)
  - 99-Pensions, S10095, A11891, 06/28/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 142)
  - Endorsement of political candidates by NYS-NOW, 06/07/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 143)
  - Equitable distribution, memo to Lillian's (Kozak) task force, 06/21/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 144)
  - Patient information, A11146, 06/21/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 145)
  - Education, 1984 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 146)
  - Equal employment rights, 1984-1987 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 147)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1983-1984 (Box 3 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 148)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1984 (Box 3 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 149)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1984; 1986 (Box 3 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 150)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, Undated (Box 3 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 151)
  - Imposed joint custody, A5578, S3907, 1985-1986 (Box 3 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 152)
  - Incoming correspondence, 1985 (Box 3 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 153)
  - Legislation, 1985-1988 (Box 3 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 154)
  - Legislative agenda, 1984-1988 (Box 4 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 155)
  - Legislative priorities, 1985 (Box 4 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 156)
  - Legislative Program, 1983 (Box 4 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 157)
  - Legislative Program, 1984 (Box 4 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 158)
  - Lobby support groups, Undated (Box 4 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 159)
  - Memos being held, 1985 (Box 4 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 160)
  - Miscellaneous, 1984-1985 (Box 4 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 161)
  - Outgoing correspondence, 1985 (Box 4 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 162)
  - Pay equity, 1984-1988 (Box 4 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 163)
  - Voting record, 1984 (Box 4 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 164)
- Mailing Lists, 1982-1984; 5; 2 cubic ft.
  Arranged in chronological order.
  Computer printouts of mailing lists of NOW-NYS arranged by zip code and alphabetically thereunder.
  - Mailing Lists, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (5-Mailing Lists), Folder 1-50)
  - Mailing Lists, 1984 (Box 2 (5-Mailing Lists), Folder 1-45)
- Chapter Newsletter File, 1982-1984; 6; 1 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically by local chapter name and chronologically thereunder.
  Contains local and NYS Chapter newsletters. Some runs are incomplete. Only the Albany Chapter newsletters are deposited on a regular basis.
  - Albany Area NOW Newsletter, 1975-1988 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 1)
  - Bay Ridge NOW Newsletter, 1981-1983 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 2)
  - Bronx NOW, The Voice of, 1978-1984; 1987 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 3)
  - Brooklyn NOW Newsletter, 1977; 1983-1985; 1987 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 4)
  - Broome County NOW Newsletter, 1985-1988 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 5)
  - Buffalo NOW-Feminist Observer, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 6)
  - Central New York Times, 1983-1988 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 7)
  - Central Westchester NOW Newsletter, 1975 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 8)
  - East End NOW, Voices from, 1978 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 9)
  - Erie County Suburban Chapter-Notes, 1973-1978 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 10)
  - Farmington Valley NOW News, 1980 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 11)
  - Finger Lakes Chapter, NOW, For Later...Newsletter of the, 1988 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 12)
  - Fredonia-Dunkirk Chapter NOW News, 1973 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 13)
  - Fulton-Montgomery NOW, 1984 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 14)
  - Genessee Valley Chapter Now, The Forum, 1975 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 15)
  - Greater Rochester NOW Newsletter, 1987-1988 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 16)
  - Greater Syracuse Chapter NOW NEWS, 1977-1978; 1987 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 17)
  - Greenwich Newsletter, 1987 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 18)
  - Huntington NOW, 1984-1987 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 19)
  - Middletown NOW, 1984-1985 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 20)
  - Mid-Hudson NOW News, 1974-1988 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 21)
  - Mid-Suffolk Chapter--NOW Hear this, 1978-1984; 1987-1988 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 22)
  - Mohawk Valley NOW Times, 1984-1987 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 23)
  - Nassau NOW Times, 1976-1988 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 24)
  - Nassau NOW Times, 1976-1988 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 25)
  - Nassau NOW Times, 1976-1988 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 26)
  - National NOW Times, 1986 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 27)
  - New York City-The NOW York Woman/NOW NYC News, 1975-1988 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 28)
  - NOW New York State, 1976; 1979 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 29)
  - NOW-NYS Action Report, 1984; 1986; 1988 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 30)
  - Northern Chataugua Country Chapter NOW News, 1976 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 31)
  - Out-of-State Chapters-'C-T', 1976-1982; 1988 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 32)
  - Putnam-East Dutchess Edition, 1977 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 33)
  - Queens Newsletter, 1975-1986 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 34)
  - Rockland County Chapter, 1978 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 35)
  - Saratoga NOW Newsletter, 1983 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 36)
  - Southern Nassau, SNNOW Alert, 1985 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 37)
  - South Shore Chapter, DO It NOW, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 38)
  - Southern Westchester, NOW NEWS, 1976 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 39)
  - Sullivan County NOW Newsletter, 1987 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 40)
  - Tompkins County Chapter Newsletter, 1985-1988 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 41)
  - Ulster County NOW Newsletter, 1985 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 42)
  - Wayne County NOW Newsletter, 1978-1980 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 43)
  - Westchester NOW Newsletter, 1987(?)-1988 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 44)
  - West Point NOW Newsletter, 1976 (Box 1 (6-Chapter Newsletter File), Folder 45)
- Feminist Publications Collection, 1966-1985; 7; 1.5 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically by title and chronologically thereunder.
  The NOW-NYS Feminist Publications Collection series contains periodicals and journals issued by a wide range of women's and feminist groups. Feminist publications include Speak Out (1972-1977), Off Our Backs (1971-1979), the Spokeswoman (1970-1977), Hera (1975), and Majority Report (1972-1979), dealing with gay and lesbian rights, reproductive rights, abortion, rape and radical political ideology. The series also includes periodicals dealing with reproductive health care and civil rights such as Family Planning/Population Reporter (1975-1977), Response to Violence in the Family (1979-1981), and Perspectives (1980-1981), a civil rights quarterly. Some periodical runs are incomplete and there are two folders of miscellaneous single issue publications. It is doubtful that NOW-NYS had a formal feminist publications collection; however, such a large quantity of feminist publications were found among the boxes processed that it was decided to organize these publications into a separate series.
  - Alive, Capital District, 1980 (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 1)
  - Alive, Northeast, 1980-1981 (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 2)
  - Family Planning/Population Reporter, 1975 (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 3)
  - Family Planning/Population Reporter, 1976 (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 4)
  - Family Planning/Population Reporter, 1977 (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 5)
  - Hera, 1975 (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 6)
  - Know, Inc, 1972-1974 (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 7)
  - Know, Inc, 1975 (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 8)
  - Know, Inc, 1976 (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 9)
  - Majority Report, 1972 June-1972 December (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 10)
  - Majority Report, 1973 January-1973 April (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 11)
  - Majority Report, 1973 May-1973 December (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 12)
  - Majority Report, 1974 January-1974 April (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 13)
  - Majority Report, 1974 May-1974 August (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 14)
  - Majority Report, 1974 September-1974 December (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 15)
  - Majority Report, 1975 January-1975 April (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 16)
  - Majority Report, 1975 June-1975 September (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 17)
  - Majority Report, 1975 October-1975 December (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 18)
  - Majority Report, 1976 January-1976 May (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 19)
  - Majority Report, 1976 May-1976 September (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 20)
  - Majority Report, 1976 October-1977 May (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 21)
  - Majority Report, 1977 May-1977 December (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 22)
  - Majority Report, 1978 January-1978 February (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 23)
  - Majority Report, 1978 May-1978 October (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous Single Issues, 1972; 1974-1977 (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous Single Issues, 1982-1985 (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 26)
  - New Womans Times, 1975 (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 27)
  - New Womans Times, 1976 (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 28)
  - News on Women in Government, 1980-1981 (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 29)
  - Off Our Backs, 1971 (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 30)
  - Off Our Backs, 1972 (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 31)
  - Off Our Backs, 1974 (Box 1 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 32)
  - Off Our Backs, 1978; 1979 (Box 2 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania NOW Newsletter, 1974 (Box 2 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 2)
  - Perspectives, the Civil Rights Quarterly, 1980-1981 (Box 2 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 3)
  - Family Planning PERSPECTIVES, 1975 (Box 2 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 4)
  - Family Planning PERSPECTIVES, 1976-1977 (Box 2 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 5)
  - Planned Parenthood-World population Washington Memo, 1975-1977 (Box 2 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 6)
  - Quash, 1976 January (Box 2 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 7)
  - Response to Violence in the Family, 1979-1980 (Box 2 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 8)
  - Response to Violence in the Family, 1981 (Box 2 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 9)
  - Sane News, 1980-1982 (Box 2 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 10)
  - Speak Out, 1972 (Box 2 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 11)
  - Speak Out, 1973 (Box 2 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 12)
  - Speak Out, 1974 (Box 2 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 13)
  - Speak Out, 1975 (Box 2 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 14)
  - Speak Out, 1976 (Box 3 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 1)
  - Speak Out, 1977 (Box 3 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 2)
  - The Spokeswoman, 1970 (Box 3 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 3)
  - The Spokeswoman, 1971 (Box 3 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 4)
  - The Spokeswoman, 1972 (Box 3 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 5)
  - The Spokeswoman, 1973 (Box 3 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 6)
  - The Spokeswoman, 1974 (Box 3 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 7)
  - The Spokeswoman, 1975 (Box 3 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 8)
  - The Spokeswoman, 1976 (Box 3 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 9)
  - The Spokeswoman, 1977 (Box 3 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 10)
  - Washington Park Spirit, 1972 (Box 3 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 11)
  - Women New York, 1975 (Box 3 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 12)
  - Women New York, 1976; 1977 (Box 3 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 13)
  - Women New York, 1979-1981 (Box 3 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 14)
  - Women's Advocate, 1983 (Box 3 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 15)
  - Women's Studies Newsletter, 1973 (Box 3 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 16)
  - Women's Studies Newsletter, 1974 (Box 3 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 17)
  - Women's Studies Newsletter, 1975 (Box 3 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 18)
  - Women's Studies Newsletter, 1976 (Box 3 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 19)
  - Women's Unit News, 1970-1974 (Box 3 (7-Feminist Publications Collection), Folder 20)